

Argyrios Tsagkalidis

Date of birth: 06/05/1984

Nationality: Greek

Gender: Male

CONTACT





(+30) 6979195398

aboutme.onedice.org



ABOUT ME

Experienced IT professional with a background in systems administration, on-site support, and hardware maintenance. I hold a BSc in Electronics Engineering, complemented by certifications in C, Python, cybersecurity, SQL, Azure Cloud, and Cisco networking. Proficient in a range of technologies, including Windows and Linux systems, networking, scripting, software development, CI/CD with Docker containers, and cloud services. A problem-solver with a strong focus on optimizing IT environments, ensuring security, and delivering top-tier remote and on-prem support.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2024 - CURRENT

Global On-Site Support Engineer Capgemini Engineering | Group IT

Networking | resolving tickets | hardware maintenance | system-room maintenance | user account management | remote and on-site support

Department Global On Site Support (GOSS) | **Website** https://www.capgemini.com

2022 - 2024

NOC Systems Administrator HDL Design House

Networking | resolving tickets | hardware maintenance | user account management | security monitoring | on-site support | system-room maintenance

Department Network Operation Center (NOC) | **Website** https://www.linkedin.com/company/hdl-design-house

2018 - 2022

IT Helpdesk Target Power Group

Equipment implementation | networking | hardware maintenance | user account management | backup planning

2013 - 2018

Computer Hardware Technician Target Power Electronics

Laptop repairing and maintenance | computer diagnosing | computer assembling/ disassembling | SMD soldering | BGA reworks | IC reprogramming | technical support

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Computer Science Certificates

- Python Data Structures University of Michigan
- Azure Cloud Services for AZ-900 Microsoft
- CS50X Computer Science Harvard edX
- <u>CS50CS Cybersecurity Harvard edX</u>
- CS50P Programming with Python Harvard edX
- Networking Essentials for CCNA CISCO Network Academy

English Language Certificates

- · LRN C2 Esolnet
- FCE B2 University of Cambridge

BSc in Electronics Engineering Technological Educational Institute of Thessaloniki - Department of Electronics Engineering

- Specialization on microprocessors/microcomputers field of study.
- Internship at Papastolou Healthcare Technologies.

Thesis Appliance power usage monitor

School Graduate 1st Vocational School of Xanthi - Analogue Electronics (Field of Study)

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING AND SCRIPTING LANGUAGES

Python 3 | C | Assembly | HTML / CSS / JavaScript | SQL | Bash | PowerShell

OPERATING SYSTEMS

Windows OS since Windows '98 | Linux/Unix-based OS | Working in CLI

NOTABLE DEV TOOLS, FRAMEWORKS, AND LIBRARIES

Flask | Gunicorn | Jinja2 | SQLAlchemy | Locust | Selinium | PyPi Packaging | Bootstrap | JQuery | AJAX | Redis **DEV CLIS AND OTHER TOOLS**

Git | GitHub Actions | Docker CLI | GitHub CLI | Azure CLI | MS-SQLServer | JSON/YAML | CI/CD | CloudFlare | VS Code

NETWORKS

VPN | NGINX | Firewalls | SFTP | NAS | SSH | CISCO iOS | RouterOS | DNS | Port Forwarding | VPS SYSADMIN TOOLS

MS Azure | MS 365 | MS Intune | DC/AD/GPOs | Self-Hosted Servers | ESET Protect | ServiceNow | MantisBT | PuTT Y | Power Automate | Icinga2 | NoMachine NX Client | LogMeIN

WEB AND CMS

CMS WordPress | CMS Magento | Web Browsers

DRIVING LICENCE



Driving Licence: B

MILITARY SERVICES



Combat Support Arms - Signal Arms